welcome to another audacity tutorial in
欢迎使用中的另一本《胆识教程》
this video I'm going to show you how to
这个视频我将向你展示如何
generate audio and sounds other than
生成音频和声音
from using your microphone or importing
从使用麦克风或导入
audio we can just generate right from
我们可以直接从
within audacity so maybe you want to
大胆地说 所以也许你想
create a sound for an animation or video
为动画或视频创建声音
game or you want to generate something a
游戏 或者您想要生成一个
sound to integrate into your existing
将声音整合到您现有的
audio this is how you can do that so the
音频这就是你如何做到这一点的
easiest thing to do to get started is to
要开始使用 最简单的方法是
just generate a tone so if we go to tone
只需生成一个音调 所以如果我们转到Tone
it brings up this box it creates an
它会调出这个框 然后创建一个
audio track for us and it just says what
给我们的音轨 它只是说什么
do you want the waveform to be first of
是否要将波形设置为
all so sine is gonna be kind of smooth
所以一切都会变得很顺利
square and sawtooth are gonna be more
正方形和锯齿形将会更多
like harsh on your ears then at the
就像你耳朵上的刺耳 然后是
frequency so how many times do you want
频率那么你想要几次呢？
that wave to repeat in Hertz and so this
在赫兹中重复的那个波 所以这个
is like 440 and then the amplitude how
是440 然后是幅度如何
loud do you want it like how high do you
你想要多高的音量吗？
want the wave to go and then if we ever
想要海浪离开 然后如果我们曾经
want to change these defaults if your
如果您的
looking different than mine you can go
看起来和我的不一样 你可以走了
to manage factory presets defaults with
使用管理出厂预设默认值的步骤
lots of different effects and generate
许多不同的效果和生成
lots of the things has this manage tab
很多东西都有这个管理标签
so you can always get back to the
这样你就可以随时回到
defaults that way but I'll just hit OK
默认设置是这样 但我只需点击OK
oh and the duration mindset - 3 seconds
哦 还有持续时间思维--3秒
yours might be 30 but anyway so this is
你可能是30岁 但不管怎样 这是
a three-second long tone that sounds
三秒长的音调听起来
like this it's kind of loud kind of
就像这样 声音有点大
obnoxious we can go to effects and we
可恶的是 我们可以去特效 我们
can also apply like effects on top of
也可以在上面应用类似的效果
this if we want to so it'd be like this
如果我们想这样 就会是这样的
so that's how you can kind of start to
所以这就是你如何开始
get and create a sound by combining
通过组合来获取和创建声音
something you generate with some effects
你产生了一些效果的东西
that we've already learned chirp is
我们已经了解到啁啾是
gonna be like a tone that starts from
就像一种基调 从
one point if we just leave this all
如果我们把这一切都抛诸脑后
default it's gonna start at this
默认情况下它将从这个开始
frequency ooh and make a change like
频率哦 做个改变 就像
that that one also could get on your
那个也可能会弄到你的
nurse and then we could like you know we
护士 然后我们就可以像你知道的我们
can come in to effects and we could
可以产生效果 我们可以
reverse this if we want it to be
如果我们想让它变成这样 那就颠倒过来
different we do reverse but we guess
不同的是 我们颠倒了方向 但我们猜
what that first effects reverse and now
最初的影响是什么 现在逆转了
it's gonna go with this right like
它会像这样配上它
something falling out of the sky in your
从天上掉下来的东西在你的身体里
animation or something
动漫什么的
let's close this so what else do we have
让我们结束这一切 我们还有什么？
that we can generate we could just
我们可以产生 我们可以
generate noise if we want some like
如果我们想要一些类似的东西 就产生噪音
white noise this is gonna be quiet
白噪音这里将会很安静
so by default let's go back
因此 默认情况下 让我们返回
I played with this one a little bit by
我玩了一下这个
default it's very very loud white noise
默认是非常非常大的白噪音
yeah but we can also we can go to change
是啊 但我们也可以去换衣服
this down to the amplitude so amplitudes
这就是波幅所以波幅
like kind of a different version of the
就像一种不同版本的
word amplify right so it's the it's
单词被放大了 所以它是
actually the height of the wave but if
实际上是海浪的高度 但如果
we put some zeroes in here and make this
我们在这里加几个零 然后做这个
amplitude a much smaller number then it
一个比它小得多的数字
makes this volume much much softer too
使这卷书也变得柔和得多
that makes it much lower what else do we
这使得它变得更低 我们还能做什么
have here we can do this DT I'm not sure
有了这里 我们可以做到这一点 我不确定
what these do it's just okay and see so
这些是做什么的 只是还好 看看就知道了
there's kind of a tone I got pulled in
有一种我被拉进去的语气
quickly pulsing pulsating tone so just
跳动得很快 音调跳动得很
play with these play with generate we've
玩这些游戏 玩游戏 我们已经
got some plucks and different things
有一些勇气和不同的东西
here like a guitar string and then again
这里像一根吉他弦 然后又一次
we can change this we can select it well
我们可以改变这个 我们可以很好地选择它
in the generation it's probably the best
在这一代人中 它可能是最好的
way to to change it we can change like
改变它的方式我们可以像这样改变
what you know how long is it gonna be
你知道要多久才能到
what type of fade-out do you want to
您想要哪种类型的淡出
have like what do we want to be like
我们想成为什么样的人
this but you can also select the whole
但您也可以选择整个
thing and go to effects and apply some
东西 然后转到效果 然后应用一些
of these different effects to it that
对它的这些不同的影响
we've learned like pitch speed add some
我们已经学到了像音调速度加一些
more bass or treble to it just kind of
更低音或高音 只是有点
yeah change the sound a little bit
是啊 稍微改变一下声音
rhythm track so we get a look like a
节奏曲目 这样我们就会得到一个像
little drum sound so you can create
小小的鼓声 这样你就可以创造
instruments too if for like for using in
仪器如果喜欢的话 也可以用在
like lmms like we've learned about if
就像我们已经了解到的LMM一样
you check it out that my other tutorial
你看看我的另一个教程
so you can create like an lms sound and
所以你可以创造出像LMS一样的声音
then bring it into lmms and then
然后把它带进洛杉矶
obviously you can change a lot of these
显然你可以改变很多这些
wave settings and different settings
波形设置和不同设置
there as well so play with these you
还有 所以玩这些
know get familiar with generating and I
我知道熟悉生成
guess what's this say I haven't done
你猜我没做什么
this so add removed plugins I guess you
所以添加删除的插件 我猜你
can probably add more plugins here if
我可以在这里添加更多的插件
you're interested in using audacity in
你有兴趣使用大胆的
this method you know generating audio
这个方法你知道生成音频
rather than just rather than bringing it
而不是把它
in from your microphone or or
从你的麦克风或或
downloading something there's probably
下载一些东西
some different plugins here that we can
在这里添加一些不同的插件 我们可以
get to bring in so maybe I'll make a
所以也许我会做一个
video on that too if I learn more about
如果我了解更多关于
using that
使用该
appreciate you watching this video go
感谢您观看这段视频
ahead and like comment subscribe leave
首页>关于我们>
your questions comments below and I hope
你的问题评论下面 我希望
to see you in another video soon
很快就能在另一个视频中看到你